您已接通310-555-0...
需要帮助吗?
Can I help you?
抱歉  我...
Sorry. I...
其实  我来...
Actually, I came...
葬礼结束了吗?
Is the funeral over?
这没有葬礼 先生  只有守灵
There was no funeral, sir. Only a viewing.
一个人也没有来
Nobody showed up.
没有人?  你确定吗?
Nobody? You sure?
只有你一个 请接受我最诚恳的哀悼
Just you.My deepest condolences.
你是朋友还是家人?
Friend or family?
都不是
Neither.
要我打开吗?
Would you like me to open it up?
不
No.
不用
请自便
Take your time.
该死
Damn it.
Danielle
还有多远?
How much further?
大约一小时
About an hour.
那个无线电塔 你上次去是什么时候?
The radio tower...when was the last time you were there?
我录下求救信号的那一天
The day I recorded the message.
我会带你去那个塔  但我不会离开这里的
I'll take you to the tower, but I'm not leaving the island.
什么?
What?
在那里我已经无家可归了
There's no place for me back there.
这里才是我的家
This is my home now.
你好 Jack
Hello Jack
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
Ben说了什么?
What did Ben say?
我们能杀他了吗?
Can we kill him?
怎么才能把这个关掉?
Is it possible to turn this equipment off?
什么?
What?
阻挠岛上信号的机器 你能关掉它吗?
The equipment that's jamming the island, can you turn it off?
当然  Ben给了我们密码
Sure. Ben gave us the code.
只有你们知道吗?
You are the only ones who have it?
是啊  怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
如果这个站被淹了会怎么样?
What would happen if the station were to be flooded?
不会怎么样
Nothing.
这些设备都是防水的
The casing for the equipment is waterproof.
它们会一直运行下去
It'll keep going forever.
那你们为什么在这里?
Then why do you need to be here?
因为这是Ben的命令
Because Ben told us to.
我们只是服从命令
We were following orders.
你从来没有问过原因吗?
And you never asked why?
不  因为我相信他
No, because I trust him,
我相信Jacob
and I trust Jacob,
如果我质疑他的命令的话 这些事...
and the minute I start questioning orders, this whole thing...
我们做的一切 都会前功尽弃
everything that we're doing here...falls apart.
她说的没错
She makes an excellent point.
不要!
求你了...
Please...
抱歉 Bonnie
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
我也只是服从命令
I, too, am following orders.
不  Des!  Des!
我们需要她
We need her.
我不认为我们还有功夫...
I don't believe we've had the pleasure...
别跟他说话!
Don't talk to him!
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
占用一下你的时间
Just a moment of your time...
我们两个单独谈谈
to talk, you and me, alone.
为什么?
For what?
你刚杀了我们七个人
You've just killed seven of my people.
你至少也能给我五分钟吧
The least you can give me is five minutes.
他是一个人吗?
Is he alone?
只有两个踪迹 他和她的
There's only two sets of tracks... his and hers.
就五分钟
Five minutes.
抱歉  先生 这张处方已经不能再配药了
I'm sorry, sir, there are no more refills left on this prescription.
一定是搞错了  我...
Well, that... That's a mistake.I...
我只领过两次
I only refilled it twice.
你能再帮我看下吗?
Could you check again?
我已经查过了  Shephard医生 你已经拿过3次药了
I did check it again, Dr. Shephard,and that was the third refill,
我也无能为力
so there's nothing I can do.
我这里还有一张处方
Fine. I've got another prescription right here.
我认识你
Hey, I know you.
-你是那个英雄  -我才不是什么英雄
-You're the hero.  -I'm not a hero.
我们在电视上看到过
We saw it on TV.
女士  你怎么回事?
Hey, lady, what's wrong with you?
他要什么就给他吧 知道他做了什么吗?
Give this guy whatever he needs.You know what he did?
是这个...
Here, just... Here...
复方羟氢可待因
Oxycodone.
Shephard医生 你不能给自己开处方
Dr. Shephard, you can't write a prescription for yourself.
这又不是给我的
That's not me.
是给Christian Shephard医生的
That's Dr.Christian Shephard.
我是Jack Shephard医生
I'm Dr.Jack Shephard.
他是我父亲
He's my father.
我得给你父亲办公室 打电话来确认一下
I'm gonna call his office to confirm...
他已经出城了
He's out of town right now.
办公室总有人...
I'm sure somebody in the office...
别麻烦了
Don't bother.
请坐
Have a seat.
Jack 不久前我做了个决定
Not so long ago, Jack,I made a decision
决定在一天内 夺走四十多个人的生命
that took the lives of over 40 people in a single day.
我告诉你是因为...
I'm telling you this because...
这里  历史还会重演
history is about to repeat itself right here,right now.
我猜  你们...
Let me guess. You've...
已经包围了我们 如果我不照做的话  你们...
You've got us surrounded,and if I don't do what you say,
你们就会杀死我们所有人
You're gonna kill all my people.
不 Jack
No, Jack.
是你
You are.
我怎么会呢?
And how am I gonna do that?
和你一起来的那个女人
The woman you're traveling with...
从直升机跳伞下来的那个女人
the one who parachuted onto the island from a helicopter...
她不是她所说的那个人
she's not who she says she is.
不是吗?
She's not, huh?
没错
No, she's not.
那她是谁?
Then who is she?
她代表想找到这座岛的人
She's a representative of some people who have been trying to find this island.
她是个坏人
She's one of the bad guys.
我差点忘了  你们是...
I almost forgot. You're the...
你们都是好人
You're the good guys.
Jack 听我说
Jack, listen to me.
如果你联络她的船 这座岛上所有的生物都会死的
If you phone her boat,every single living person on this island will be killed.
这样吧
So here's what has to happen.
把那个设备
Get that device...
她随身带着的那个电话
the phone she carries with her...
交给我
and give it to me.
我就会转过身去
I will turn around.
你走你的独木桥
We'll go back to my people.
我走我的阳关道
You will turn around,go back to your people.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
-能把对讲机还给我吗?  -什么?
-May I have my walkie back?  -What?
有些东西你一定很想听
There's something you need to hear.
拜托?
Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
Tom 你在吗?
Tom, are you there?
是的
Yeah, I'm here.
你们害死了我们七个人
Your plan killed seven of my people,
但没有死的 正抓着你的朋友
but the ones that you failed to kill are now holding your friends
Jin  Sayid  Bernard 都在枪口上
Jin, Sayid, Bernard, at gunpoint.
Jack 别给他任何... 啊!  住手!
Jak,don't give him any...
给我闭嘴!
I said shut up
我现在就掐断你的脖子...
And what's to stop me from snapping your neck...
Tom 如果我一分钟之内还没发话 就把他们三个都杀了
Tom, unless you hear my voice in one minute, shoot all three of them.
收到
got it!
我说了别动!
I said don't move!
把电话给我
Bring me the phone.
不要和他们谈条件!
40秒
40 seconds.
不
No.
我要把他们带出这座岛 他们所有人!
I'm getting them all off the island. All of 'em!
我想问问你
Let me ask you something.
为什么你想离开这里?
Why do you want to leave the island?
是什么让你如此 迫不及待的想要回去?
What is it you so desperately wanna get back to?
你一无所有了
You have no one.
你父亲死了  妻子也和别人好了
Your father's dead. Your wife left you,moved on with another man.
你难道非得回到医院  继续救死扶伤吗?
Can you just not wait to get back to the hospital,get back to fixing things?
还剩20秒
It's 20 seconds now.
-只要把电话给我   -不
-Just get me the phone.   -no
10秒
Ten seconds.
-把电话给我  -不
-Bring me the phone.  -No.
-我说到做到 -你休想!
-I'm not bluffing.  -I won't...do it!
5...4...3...
Five...Four... three...
不
no
我很抱歉Jack
I'm so sorry, Jack.
Tom你在吗?
Tom, are you there?
是的 Jack  我听见了
Yeah, Jack, I hear you.
我要带他们去无线电塔
I'm gonna lead my people up to the radio tower,
然后拨打那个电话
and I'm gonna make a call,
我要让大家都得救 所有人
and I'm gonna get'em all rescued.Every one of'em.
然后我会来找你...
And then I'm gonna come find you...
然后杀了你
and I'm gonna kill you.
现在你可以报复Ben了
You have the opportunity to make Ben very, very angry.
为什么不呢?
Why would you not take that?
-5..4..5...   -什么?
-5..-4..5...  -What?
-8..7..7   -这是密码吗?
- 8..7..5..5  -Is that a code?
-5..5..4..3..7...  -慢点  从头说起
-5..4..3..7...  -Wait.Start again, start again.
-6...  -再说一遍
-6...  -Start from the beginning!
-1..1..3   -再说一遍
-1..1..3   -Start from the beginning.
Bonnie!  Bonnie!
醒醒  醒醒
Wake up, wake up.
再说一遍
Start again.
-Good vibrations  -什么?
-Good vibrations.  -What?
Beach Boys (沙滩男孩  一摇滚乐队)
"Good vibrations"
在键盘上
On the keypad.
那些数字...
The numbers...
就是音符
they're notes.
这个程序是  一个音乐家设计的
It was programmed by a musician.
把他绑起来
Tie him up.
把他一起带上
He's coming with us.
什么?
What?
Alex
这是你母亲
This is your mother.
可以帮我把他绑起来吗?
Will you help me tie him up?
怎么了?  他都说了什么?
What happened? What'd he say?
已经不重要了
It's not important right now.
-把大家集合起来  -Jack你的手
-Just get everybody together.  -Jack, your knuckles.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
他杀了他们
He killed them.
Bernard...
Jin  Sayid  他们3个...
Jin  Sayid. All three of'em. He...
他和海滩上的人取得联系
He radioed the beach.
而我什么都做不了
And I let it happen.
我只能这么做
I had to let it happen.
我们不能让Rose知道...
We can't tell Rose...
还有Sun 至少现在不行
or Sun, not yet.
我们得出发了  我答应Sayid我们会继续前进
We gotta keep moving. I promised Sayid that we would keep moving.
为什么把他带来?
So why did you bring him back?
怎么不直接杀了他?
Why didn't you just kill him?
因为我想让他目睹...
Because I want him to see it.
我们离开岛上的那一刻
I want him to experience the moment that we get off this island,
我还要让他知道...
and I want him to know...
他失败了
That he failed.
然后我会杀了他
And then I'll kill him.
那是命令 Tom
It was an order, Tom.
我们必须服从
We had to follow it.
Ben根本就不知道自己在说什么
Ben didn't know what the hell he's talking about.
他已经糊涂了
He's lost it.
看他对我们都做了什么
I mean, look at what they did to us!
我们不该往沙子里开抢
Instead of putting three bullets in the damn sand,
应该直接杀了他们
we should've killed them for real.
他们只有三个人和四把枪
All they got left is three guys and four guns.
可我们只有两个人  一把枪也没有
And all we've got, James,are two people and no guns.
那我们等到晚上
So we'll wait till night.
到了那时我们还是 无能为力
That isn't gonna change the fact that we're unarmed.
如果你想送死  请自便 但在这之前...
If you wanna kill yourself, that's fine,but before you go and try...
听见了吗?
You hear that?
Ryan!
等等  英雄
Stay in the bus, hero.
别动 Tom
Stay right there, Tom.
好吧
ok
我投降
I give up.
这枪是为了那个 被你拽下木筏的孩子
That's for taking the kid off the raft.
老兄  他已经投降了
Dude, it was over. He surrendered.
我不相信他
I didn't believe him.
你在干什么  Shephard医生?
What are you doing, Dr.Shephard?
我只是...
I was just...
想看一下...
I was just checking the...
Arlen的情况... 我想看看...
The Arlen charts. Just wanted to...
手术的如何
Wanted to see how the operation went.
我给你留了三条语音信息 你没收到吗?
I left three messages on your voice mail. You didn't get them?
我电话坏了
My phone's broken.
到我办公室来一下
Let's go to my office.
-干吗?  -我们得谈谈
-For what?  -We need to have a talk. Come on.
你...你是新来的
You're new around here,
-还不真正了解我  -我知道的够多的了
-so you don't know much about me...  -I know enough.
-还是到我办公室来一下吧  -有话就直说吧!
-So let's go to my office...  -If you got something to say to me,say it to me
就在这里
Right here.
能离开会儿吗?
Will you excuse us, please?
你救了的那个女人Arlen太太 两小时前醒过来了
Mrs. Arlen, the woman you saved,woke up in recovery about two hours ago.
她还有些疼痛  不过神智完全清醒
She was in some pain but highly responsive to the reflex tests and entirely lucid.
很好啊
Well, that's...That's great.
她也回忆起了事发经过
But then she described the series of events that caused her accident.
她说她正在桥上行驶 看见桥上站着个人
She says she was driving over the bridge when she saw a man standing on top of the railing
正准备往下跳
about to jump off.
她分了神  车子失了控
She was distracted and lost control of her car.
她开进了隔离带  后面的货车就撞上了她
She ran into the median,rolled over and was hit by the van behind her.
所以问题很明显...
So the obvious question here...
为什么你那么快就 到了事发现场?
It's how did you get to that flaming car so fast?
你在那桥上做什么?
What were you doing on that bridge?
你知道我在这医院 工作了多久吗?
Do you know how many years I've worked at this hospital?
你了解我吗?
Do you know...anything about me?
你知不知道...
Do you have any idea...
我都经历了些什么?
what I've been through?
你今天喝了多少?
How much have you had to drink today?
好吧 我来告诉你怎么做
Okay,I'll tell you what. You do this...
你现在把我父亲叫下来
You get my father down here.
如果我比他还醉的话 你就可以开除我了
Get him down here right now,and if I'm drunker than he is,you can fire me.
别用这种眼神看着我 别...可怜我
Don't you look at me like that.Don't you... pity me.
-我只是想帮你  -你帮不了我!
-I'm trying to help you...  -You can't help me!
注意了  蠢蛋们
Attention, Others. Come in, Others.
你们在那边的话 听好了  你们输了
If you're listening to this,I want you to know that we got you bastards,
你们还想活的话 就离我们的海滩远远的
the rest of you wanna be blown up,you best stay away from our beach.
Hurley?
Jack?
你在哪? 怎么回事?
Where are you? What's going on?
-我回到海滩了 老兄  -什么?
-Dude, I'm back at the beach.  -What?
我回来帮Juliet和Sawyer
I went back to help Juliet and Sawyer.
我救了他们
I saved them.
他们还好吗?
They're okay?
-Juliet...  -都没事
-Juliet...  -Everyone's fine.
我  Sawyer  Juliet  Sayid  Jin  Bernard
Me, Sawyer, Juliet, Sayid, Jin, Bernard.
-我们都...  -等一下
-We all  -Wait.
Bernard  Jin还有Sayid 都和你们在一起?
Bernard and Jin and Sayid...They're with you?
是的  老兄 我救了他们
Yeah, dude, I told you.I saved them all.
你们先待在那 我们快到塔那里了
Stay where you are.We're almost up to the tower.
-你们在那里很安全  -没问题
-You'll be safer there.  -Yeah, I gotcha.
我们不会走开的 直到我们收到"家"的信号
We'll stay put until you like,you know, phone home.
Charlie怎么样了? 他回来了吗?
What about Charlie?Did he make it back yet?
还没有  但他们 随时都会回来的
Not yet, but they're probably paddling home as we speak.
别担心  他会没事的
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine.
Des...
那是潜水装备吗?
There's diving gear on those racks, yeah?
是的  还有很多
Aye. It's plenty.
不如你去准备那些 我来弹"Good Vibrations"
Why don't you take care of that? I'll tap out Good Vibrations.
好的  伙计
Alright, mate.
Des
有什么幻觉吗?
You get any flashes?
没有
No. Nothin'.
-等会在这里碰头  -好的
-I'll meet you back here,then. -Ok.
我的命运到此为止
So much for fate.
"信号传入"?
"Incoming transmission"?
听得见吗?
Can you hear me ?
听得见
Yes! Yes, I can hear you.
你是谁?  我在和谁说话?
Who is this? Who am I speaking to?
Charlie!  Charlie Pace
我是815航班的幸存者 815航班
I'm a survivor of flight 8-1-5... Oceanic, flight 8-1-5.
你在哪?
Where are you?
-我们在一个岛上 我们还活着  -岛上? 是什么地方?
-We're on an island. We're alive.  -An island? Well, where?
-具体在什么方位?  -我不知道  你是谁?
-What's the location?  -I don't know. Who's this?
我是Penelope Penelope  Widmore
This is Penelope,Penelope Widmore.
你怎么收到信号的?
How did you get this frequency?
Desmond!
-你在说Desmond吗?  -他在这 和我在一起
-Did you just say, "Desmond"?  -Yeah, he's here,he's with me.
-他还好吗?  -好极了
-Is he okay?  -He's brilliant!
-你在船上吗?  -什么船?
-Hey, are you on the boat?  -What boat?
你的船啊  离海岸80英里
Your boat...80 miles offshore.
-Naomi 那个跳伞的  -我不在船上
-Naomi, parachutist.  -I'm not on a boat.
谁又是Naomi?
Who's Naomi?
你能听见我吗?
Can you hear me?
Penny!不!
Charlie!
不是Penny的船
Aaron 没事的  宝贝
Hey, Aaron, it's okay, sweetie.
-他怎么了?  -我不知道
-What's the matter?  -I don't know.
我猜他有些害怕了
I think he's just a bit scared.
-别怪孩子  -怎么了?
-Hard to blame him.  -What is it?
你男朋友叫什么? 那个去水下的摇滚巨星
What's your boyfriend's name...The rock star who goes to the station?
是Charlie 怎么了?
Charlie. Why?
Charlie让我们获救了
Charlie just got us rescued.
他成功了!
He did it!
-你朋友做到了  -什么?
-Your friend bloody well did it.  -What?
绿灯亮了  没有干扰了
The green light... it's on.The jamming stopped.
-试试看  -好的
-Use it, then.  -Alright.
4-4-2
il est dehors  Il est dehorset brennan pris les clefs(法语)
这是什么?
What's this?
是Rousseau的求救信号 它还在干扰
It's Rousseau's message.It's still blocking the signal.
没关系  我们已经到了
It doesn't matter. We're here.
1-7-5-5-0-4-4-5
il est dehors Il est dehors et brennan pris les clefs(法语)
Veuillez nous aider Ils sont morts(法语)
Ils sont tous morts.Aidez-nous Ils sont morts(法语)
这是我十六年前录下的
I recorded this 16 years ago.
就在你出生的三天前
Three days before you were born.
Il est dehors Il est dehors et brennan pris les clefs Veuiez nous aider(法语)
我们已经不需要它了
I guess we don't need it anymore.
好了  干吧
All right. Do it.
这里收不到信号
I can't get a signal in here.
有反应了
I'm getting something.
一定能行的
It's gonna work.
我们终于要离开这个岛了
It's happening.We're gonna get off of this island.
回了家 我们一定要好好庆祝
We'll celebrate when we're home.
Jack!
你以为是在救大家 但你得停下
I know you think you're saving your people,but you need to stop this.
-这是个错误  -听你的话才是错误
-It's a mistake.  -The mistake was listening to you.
这是你最后的机会
This will be your last chance.
听我说  打通那个电话 将是末日的开始
I'm telling you, making that call is the beginning of the end.
收到了  我收到信号了
I've got it! I've got a signal!
Jack 求你了  你根本不知道自己在做什么
Jack, please!You don't know what you're doing!
我很清楚自己在做什么
I know exactly what I'm doing.
John!
退后Jack
Step back, Jack.
-你都做了些什么?  -做了我必须做的
-What did you do?  -What I had to.
退后
Now step back.
离电话远点
Stay away from the phone.
-你在干什么John?  -我不想对你开枪
-What are you doing?  -I don't want to shoot you.
开枪啊 John!
Do it, John! Shoot him!
请把电话放下
Please, put the phone down.
不  你别想让我 再留在这座岛上了
No,you're done keeping me on this island
如果有必要的话 我会杀了你
I will...kill you...if I have to.
开枪啊
Then do it.
Jack
你不该这么做的
You're not supposed to do this.
Minkowski
-你是谁?  -你又是谁?
-Who is this?  -Who is this?
我叫Jack Shephard  你是...
My name's Jack Shephard. Are you...
货船上的人吗?
Are you on the boat... the freighter?
你怎么连上 这个频道的?
How'd you get this channel?
Naomi  Naomi告诉我们你们的搜救小组 还有船的事
Naomi told us about your search team,about the boat.
Naomi?  你找到她了?
Naomi? You found her?
她在哪?  你是什么人?
Where is she? Who are you?
我是815航班的幸存者之一
I'm one of the survivors of oceanic flight 815.
你能确定我们的方位吗?
Can you get a fix on our location?
当然可以  你们呆在那儿
Hell, yeah, we can. Sit tight.
我们会来的
We'll be right there.
是我  等等
It's me. Wait.
求你别挂
Don't... Don't hang up, please.
我知道你说过  我只是...
I know what you said. I just...
我想见见你  求你了
I just need to see you,please.
机场外
Yeah, out at the airport.
在老地方见
You know where.
谢谢
Thank you.
在新闻里看到你了
Saw you on the news.
还在救人啊
Still pulling people out of burning wreckage, huh?
老习惯了
Old habits.
-你看起来糟透了  -是啊
-You look terrible.  -Yeah
谢谢
Thanks.
为什么打电话给我?
Why did you call me?
我想你也听说了  也许你会出席葬礼
I was hoping that you'd heard,that maybe you'd go to the funeral.
我干嘛要出席葬礼?
Why would I go to the funeral?
-经常坐飞机  -什么?
-Been flying a lot.  -What?
他们给我张金卡
The golden pass that they gave us.
我一直在用
I've been using it.
每周5晚上  我...
Every friday night, I...
从洛杉矶飞到东京...
I fly from L.A. to Tokyo or...
新加坡...悉尼
Singapore or... Sydney.
下了飞机   我就...
I get off, and I...
喝个饱  然后再飞回家
have a drink and then I fly home.
为什么?
Why?
因为我希望它坠毁
Because I want it to crash.
我不在乎飞机上的其他人
I don't care about anybody else on board.
每次遇上小颠簸  或者...
Every little bump we hit or...
暖流  我都会闭上眼睛
turbulence, I mean, like,I actually close my eyes,
祈祷着我能回到从前
and I pray that I can get back...
-这已经无法改变了   -不  我讨厌说谎的人
-This is not gonna change...  -No, I'm sick...of lying.
我们犯了个错
We made a mistake.
我得走了  免得他起疑心
I have to go.He's gonna be wondering where I am...
我们不该离开
We were not supposed to leave.
不  我们应该
Yes, we were.
再见 Jack
Goodbye, Jack.
我们得回去 Kate
We have to go back, Kate.
我们得回去!
We have to go back!
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■